{
    "id": "b3790ef7ca0140e9b5d3c79e6a19d3ac",
    "title": "Gap Fills",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The auditorium was ............................ with buntings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "decorating",
                "decorated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "688b29d295f44b6ba94b478fe869d82d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Chairs ............................. neatly arranged in rows for the invitees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6905749609364471950498f2588cc443"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dais ........................ a beautiful backdrop.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d49844ac60ed4ab2b95e3ab36b9a84cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The principal .......................... the chief guest to the stage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "escorted",
                "was escorted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e98e1cfbe0d14384aa4c8a1b6d6e0149"
        },
        {
            "question": "When they .............................. their seats, two girls sang the prayer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all occupied",
                "were all occupied"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3bab03da7489410b9caebcd26b711325"
        },
        {
            "question": "After that the principal ............................ the annual report.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was reading",
                "read"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2cbe91ec19fc4d5393b999b38e5516cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Then the chief guest ........................... a brief speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "was made",
                "has made"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "866264d5ac484478873489aafa22cc82"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .............................. the students to work hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was advising",
                "has advised",
                "advised"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2a1d589707954eeeaa76860cd90d7af3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that they should aim at success and ............................ credit to the school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "bringing",
                "brought"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a3d8b41849134cc2b0ce5f6592751bed"
        },
        {
            "question": "This ........................... by the prize distribution ceremony.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "followed",
                "was followed",
                "has followed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f93b94fccc543bc8403c58be563f037"
        }
    ]
}